Guide to the Paul Langland Papers, 1926-2018 MSS.253
Fales Library and Special Collections
- OVERSIZE Series IV: Posters, Programs and Flyers, 1975-2000
  Series IV is arranged into two subseries, reflecting Paul Langland's original organization. Subseries A is arranged by artist and Subseries B is arranged by venue. Any additional material that was not assigned an original category has been arranged alphabetically by venue, and is listed at the end of the series.
  Oversize Series IV consists of oversize posters for various dance and arts performances and events. It largely consists of material related to New York City venues from the mid 1970s through the 1990s, but also includes other localities. Included in this series is material related to many noted New York City performance spaces and groups, including Danspace, Dance Theater Workshop, LaMama, and Movement Research. Due to the nature of the type of material, many of the posters do not include a year.
  - Subseries A: Artists, 1975-2000
    - Laurie Anderson, undated; cuid29293 (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - Bread and Puppet Theater, 1982; cuid29294 (Box 26, Folder 13)
    - Tricia Brown, 1987; undated; cuid29295 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Channel Z, 1984-1987; cuid29296 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Ping Chong, 1986; 1992; cuid29297 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Lucinda Childs, undated; cuid29298 (Folder 1)
    - Contact Improv, 1975; 1977-1979; 1983; cuid29299 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Ellen Fisher, undated; cuid29300 (Folder 1)
    - Simone Forti, undated; cuid29301 (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Grand Union, undated; cuid29302 (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Paul Langland, 1983-1984; 1986; 1988-1998; 2000; undated; cuid29303 (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - Paul Langland, undated; cuid29304 (Folder 1)
    - Daniel Lepkoff, 1979; 1989; undated; cuid29305 (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - Nina Martin, undated; cuid29306 (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - Meredith Monk, 1979; 1982; 1984; 1986; 1991; cuid29307 (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - Meredith Monk, 1998; undated; cuid29308 (Box 27, Folder 11)
    - Meredith Monk, 1985; cuid29309 (Folder 1)
    - Mary Overlie, 1998; undated; cuid29310 (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - Steve Paxton, undated; cuid29311 (Box 27, Folder 13)
    - Stephen Petronio, undated; cuid29312 (Box 27, Folder 14)
    - Stephen Petronio, undated; cuid29313 (Folder 1)
    - Diane Torr, undated; cuid29314 (Box 27, Folder 15)
    - David Zambrano, undated; cuid29315 (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - Marian Zazeela, 1981; cuid29316 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Subseries B: Venues, 1977-2009, undated
    - BAM [Brooklyn Academy of Music], 1983, 1986-1988; cuid29317 (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - Danspace, 1984-1987; 1996-1997; 1999; cuid29318 (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - Dance Theater Workshop, 1986-1988; cuid29319 (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - La Mama, undated; cuid29320 (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - Movement Research, 1984-1985; 1988; 1993-1994; cuid29321 (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - Movement Research, 1987; cuid29322 (Folder 1)
    - NYU Experimental Theater Wing/Tisch School of the Arts, 2009; undated; cuid29323 (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - NYU Experimental Theater Wing/Tisch School of the Arts, undated; cuid29324 (Folder 1)
    - PS 122, 1981; 1984; 1988; cuid29325 (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - Whitney Museum of Art, undated; cuid29326 (Folder 1)
    - Venues A-Z, 1977; 1980-1984; 1989-1990; 1998; 2000; undated; cuid29327 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - General Posters
    - General Poster, undated; cuid29328 (Folder 1)
- OVERSIZE Series V: Allan Wayne Material, undated
  Oversize Series V consists of several performance posters featuring Allan Wayne.
  - Allan Wayne Material, undated; cuid29329 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - [Allan Wayne- Theater Dance Poster], undated; cuid29330 (Box 28, Folder 12)